Bill Pelke Papers
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- General Activism, 1984-2000, Undated; nam_apap205-6; 5.08 cubic feet
  - Friends Committee to Abolish the Death Penalty -The Quaker Abolitionist, 1997; nam_apap205-6_144 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Friends Committee to Abolish the Death Penalty -The Quaker Abolitionist, 1997; nam_apap205-6_145 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Friends Committee to Abolish the Death Penalty -The Quaker Abolitionist, 1998; nam_apap205-6_146 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Friends Outside - The Liaison Quarterly, 1993; nam_apap205-6_147 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Friends Outside - The Liaison Quarterly, 1993; nam_apap205-6_148 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Friends Outside - The Liaison Quarterly, 1994; nam_apap205-6_149 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Friends Outside - The Liaison Quarterly, 1994; nam_apap205-6_150 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Friends Outside - The Liaison Quarterly, 1994; nam_apap205-6_151 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Friends Outside - The Liaison Quarterly, 1994; nam_apap205-6_152 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Friends Outside - The Liaison Quarterly, 1995; nam_apap205-6_153 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Friends Outside - The Liaison Quarterly, 1995; nam_apap205-6_154 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - From Blues to Blessings Ministries, Undated; nam_apap205-6_155 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Fund for Life News and Notes, 1995; nam_apap205-6_156 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Gary Graham Justice Coalition, 1993-1994; Undated; nam_apap205-6_157 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - The Gathering, 1994; nam_apap205-6_158 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - The Gathering, 1994; nam_apap205-6_159 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - The Gathering, 1995; nam_apap205-6_160 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - GEM Ministries, 1993-1994; nam_apap205-6_161 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Generation Action, 1998; nam_apap205-6_162 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Graterfriends, 1992; nam_apap205-6_163 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Graterfriends, 1992; nam_apap205-6_164 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Graterfriends, 1993; nam_apap205-6_165 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Graterfriends, 1993; nam_apap205-6_166 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Graterfriends, 1993; nam_apap205-6_167 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Graterfriends, 1994; nam_apap205-6_168 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Graterfriends, 1994; nam_apap205-6_169 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Graterfriends, 1995; nam_apap205-6_170 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Graterfriends, 1995; nam_apap205-6_171 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Graterfriends, 1995; nam_apap205-6_172 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Graterfriends, 1996; nam_apap205-6_173 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Graterfriends, 1996; nam_apap205-6_174 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Graterfriends, 1997; nam_apap205-6_175 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Graterfriends, 1997; nam_apap205-6_176 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Graterfriends, 1997; nam_apap205-6_177 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Graterfriends, 1998; nam_apap205-6_178 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Graterfriends, 1998; nam_apap205-6_179 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Graterfriends, 1998; nam_apap205-6_180 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Graterfriends, 1999; nam_apap205-6_181 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Graterfriends, 1999; nam_apap205-6_182 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Hansen House of Hospitality and Criminal Justice Ministries -Bars and Stripes, 1990; 1992; nam_apap205-6_183 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Harmony, 1995; nam_apap205-6_184 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Harmony, 1996; nam_apap205-6_185 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Harmony, 1997; nam_apap205-6_186 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Harmony, 1997; nam_apap205-6_187 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Hope of Cure, 1996; Undated; nam_apap205-6_188 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - The House of Prayer Newsletter, Undated; nam_apap205-6_189 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Houston Peace News, 1997; nam_apap205-6_190 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Human Kindness Foundation, Undated; nam_apap205-6_191 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Human Kindness Foundation - newsletters, 1994; nam_apap205-6_192 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Human Kindness Foundation - newsletters, 1995; nam_apap205-6_193 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Human Kindness Foundation - newsletters, 1995; nam_apap205-6_194 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Human Kindness Foundation - newsletters, 1996; nam_apap205-6_195 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Human Kindness Foundation - newsletters, 1997; nam_apap205-6_196 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Humanitas - newsletters, 1992; nam_apap205-6_197 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - I Oppose the Death Penalty: Don't Kill For Me - Button, Undated; nam_apap205-6_198 (Oversize 5, Item 11)
  - Illinois Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1992; 1994-1995; Undated; nam_apap205-6_199 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Indiana Citizens to Abolish Capital Punishment, 1998; Undated; nam_apap205-6_200 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Indiana Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1989; 1991-1992; nam_apap205-6_201 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Indiana Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty - conference packet, 1989; nam_apap205-6_202 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Indianapolis Coalition to Abolish Capital Punishment, 1998; Undated; nam_apap205-6_203 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Indianapolis Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1997-1998; nam_apap205-6_204 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Indianapolis Peach and Justice, 1997; nam_apap205-6_205 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Innocent on Death Row: The Ten Year Story of Rolando Cruz - Poster, Undated; nam_apap205-6_206 (Flat-file 4)
  - Intercommunity Justice and Peace Centers -Issues, 1994; nam_apap205-6_207 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Interfaith Pilgrimage for Peace and Life, 1994; nam_apap205-6_208 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - International Federation of Action by Christians for the Abolition of Torture, 1995; Undated; nam_apap205-6_209 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - International Federation of Action by Christians for the Abolition of Torture - The Tortured, Torturers, and Christian Hope, 1990; nam_apap205-6_210 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - International Forgiveness Institute, 1996-1997; nam_apap205-6_211 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Iowa's Democratoc Left Newsletter -The Prairie Progressive, 1992; nam_apap205-6_212 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Iowans Against the Death Penalty, 1992-1995; 1997-1998; Undated; nam_apap205-6_213 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Jubilee Partners, 1997-1998; nam_apap205-6_214 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Justice Report, 1992-1997; Undated; nam_apap205-6_215 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Kansas Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1991; 1996; Undated; nam_apap205-6_216 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - La Voz, 1993; nam_apap205-6_217 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - The Lamp of Hope Project, 1993-1995; 1997; Undated; nam_apap205-6_218 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Liberarsi dalla necessita del carcere, 1994; nam_apap205-6_219 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Life Advocate, 1993; nam_apap205-6_220 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - LifeLines, 1993-1994; nam_apap205-6_221 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - LifeLines - The Wing of Friendship, 1994; nam_apap205-6_222 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Lighting the Torch of Conscience, 1989-1990; Undated; nam_apap205-6_223 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Lighting the Torch of Conscience - packet, 1990; nam_apap205-6_224 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Lionheart Foundation, 1994; nam_apap205-6_225 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Lionheart Foundation, 1994; nam_apap205-6_226 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Lionheart Foundation, Undated; nam_apap205-6_227 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - The Lionheart Foundation Newsletter, 1993-1994; nam_apap205-6_228 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Live and Let Live, 1993; nam_apap205-6_229 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Lousiana Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty -The Pilgrimage, 1997; nam_apap205-6_230 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Lousiana Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty -The Pilgrimage, 1998; nam_apap205-6_231 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Lousiana Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty -The Pilgrimage, 1998; nam_apap205-6_232 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Love over Vengeance, Undated; nam_apap205-6_233 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Massachusetts Citizens Against the Death Penalty, 1990; Undated; nam_apap205-6_234 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - The Mediator, 1994-1995; nam_apap205-6_235 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Mennonite Central Committee, 1992-1995; Undated; nam_apap205-6_236 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Mid - Missouri Fellowship for Reconciliation, Undated; nam_apap205-6_237 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Mid - Missouri Fellowship for Reconciliation -FOR News, 1998; nam_apap205-6_238 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Mid - Missouri Fellowship for Reconciliation -FOR News, 1998; nam_apap205-6_239 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Mid - Missouri Fellowship for Reconciliation -FOR News, 1998; nam_apap205-6_240 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Mid - Missouri Fellowship for Reconciliation -FOR News, 1999; nam_apap205-6_241 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Millions to Kill, Pennies to Heal Banner, Undated; nam_apap205-6_242 (Oversize 5, Item 13)
  - Minnesota Advocates for Human Rights, 1993; 1995-1997; nam_apap205-6_243 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Minnesota Advocates for Human Rights -Human Rights Observer, 1996; nam_apap205-6_244 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Minnesota Advocates for Human Rights -Human Rights Observer, 1996; nam_apap205-6_245 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Minnesota Advocates for Human Rights -Human Rights Observer, 1997; nam_apap205-6_246 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Minnesota Advocates for Human Rights -Human Rights Observer, 1999; nam_apap205-6_247 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Missions and Mental Health Conference -Forgiveness in Healing Wounded Servants, 1992; nam_apap205-6_248 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund, 1990; 1992-1994; 1996; Undated; nam_apap205-6_249 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund - Death Row, U.S.A., 1991-1994; 1997; nam_apap205-6_250 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Napier Network, 1993-1995; 1993/1995; nam_apap205-6_251 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - National Alliance Against Racist and Political Oppression -Organizer, 1994; nam_apap205-6_252 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - National Campaign to Stop Control Unit Prisons, 1995; nam_apap205-6_253 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - National Commission on Capital Punishment, Undated; nam_apap205-6_254 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - National Conference on Forgiveness, 1995; nam_apap205-6_255 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - National Conference on Forgiveness in Clinical Practice, 1996; nam_apap205-6_256 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - National Conference on Forgiveness Packet, 1995; nam_apap205-6_257 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - National Conference on Wrongful Convictions and the Death Penalty, 1998; nam_apap205-6_258 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - National CURE, 1991; nam_apap205-6_259 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - National CURE, 1992; nam_apap205-6_260 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - National CURE, 1993; nam_apap205-6_261 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - National CURE, 1994; nam_apap205-6_262 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - National CURE, 1995; nam_apap205-6_263 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - National CURE, 1996; nam_apap205-6_264 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - National CURE, 1997; nam_apap205-6_265 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - National CURE, 1998-2000; Undated; nam_apap205-6_266 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - National Lawyers Guild - Prison Law Project, 1994; nam_apap205-6_267 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - National Lawyers Guild - Prison Law Project, 1995; nam_apap205-6_268 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - National Lawyers Guild - Prison Law Project, 1996; nam_apap205-6_269 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - National Lawyers Guild - Prison Law Project, 1997; nam_apap205-6_270 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - National Lawyers Guild - Prison Law Project, 1997; nam_apap205-6_271 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - National Organizing Committee, 1993-1994; Undated; nam_apap205-6_272 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - National Organizing Committee -People's Tribune, 1993; nam_apap205-6_273 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - National Organizing Committee -People's Tribune, 1993; nam_apap205-6_274 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - National Organizing Committee -People's Tribune, 1994; nam_apap205-6_275 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - National Organizing Committee -People's Tribune, 1994; nam_apap205-6_276 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - National Organizing Committee -People's Tribune, 1995; nam_apap205-6_277 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - National Organizing Committee -People's Tribune, 1995; nam_apap205-6_278 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - National Organizing Committee -Tribuno del Pueblo, 1993; nam_apap205-6_279 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Nebraska Coalition for Victims of Crimes - newsletters, 1992-1995; nam_apap205-6_280 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty, 1991-1996; Undated; nam_apap205-6_281 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1994; nam_apap205-6_282 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1994; nam_apap205-6_283 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1995; nam_apap205-6_284 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1995; nam_apap205-6_285 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1995; nam_apap205-6_286 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1996; nam_apap205-6_287 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1996; nam_apap205-6_288 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1996; nam_apap205-6_289 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1996; nam_apap205-6_290 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1996; nam_apap205-6_291 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1997; nam_apap205-6_292 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1998; nam_apap205-6_293 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1998; nam_apap205-6_294 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Nebraskans Against the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1998; nam_apap205-6_295 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - New Hope House, 1990; Undated; nam_apap205-6_296 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1989; nam_apap205-6_297 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1990; nam_apap205-6_298 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1991; nam_apap205-6_299 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1991; nam_apap205-6_300 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1991; nam_apap205-6_301 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1992; nam_apap205-6_302 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1992; nam_apap205-6_303 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1992; nam_apap205-6_304 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1992; nam_apap205-6_305 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1992; nam_apap205-6_306 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1993; nam_apap205-6_307 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1993; nam_apap205-6_308 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1993; nam_apap205-6_309 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1993; nam_apap205-6_310 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1994; nam_apap205-6_311 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1994; nam_apap205-6_312 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1994; nam_apap205-6_313 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1994; nam_apap205-6_314 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1994; nam_apap205-6_315 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1995; nam_apap205-6_316 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1995; nam_apap205-6_317 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1995; nam_apap205-6_318 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1995; nam_apap205-6_319 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1996; nam_apap205-6_320 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1996; nam_apap205-6_321 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1996; nam_apap205-6_322 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1996; nam_apap205-6_323 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1997; nam_apap205-6_324 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1997; nam_apap205-6_325 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1997; nam_apap205-6_326 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1997; nam_apap205-6_327 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1998; nam_apap205-6_328 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1998; nam_apap205-6_329 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1998; nam_apap205-6_330 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1998; nam_apap205-6_331 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - New Hope House - newsletter, 1999; nam_apap205-6_332 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - The New Party, 1993; nam_apap205-6_333 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Northern Indiana Coalition Against the Death Penalty, 1996-1998; Undated; nam_apap205-6_334 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Northwest Indiana Coalition to Abolish Control Unit Prisons, 1996-1997; nam_apap205-6_335 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Northwest Indiana Federation of Labor -The Voice, 1992; nam_apap205-6_336 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Northwest Indiana Steering Committee to Stop Supermaximum Prisons, 1996; nam_apap205-6_337 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - NYS Coalition for Criminal Justice -NYSCCJ Update, 1992; nam_apap205-6_338 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Odyssey: Creative Alternatives in Criminal Justice, 1992; nam_apap205-6_339 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Offender Victim Ministries, Inc. -OVM Newsletter, 1991; nam_apap205-6_340 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Ohio Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, Undated; nam_apap205-6_341 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Ohioans to Stop Executions -The Stoppit, 1998; nam_apap205-6_342 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Ohioans to Stop Executions -The Stoppit, 1998; nam_apap205-6_343 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Ohioans to Stop Executions -The Stoppit, 1998; nam_apap205-6_344 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Ohioans to Stop Executions -The Stoppit, 1998; nam_apap205-6_345 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - The Open Door Community, 1991-1995; Undated; nam_apap205-6_346 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1990; nam_apap205-6_347 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1991; nam_apap205-6_348 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1991; nam_apap205-6_349 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1991; nam_apap205-6_350 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1992; nam_apap205-6_351 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1993; nam_apap205-6_352 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1994; nam_apap205-6_353 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1994; nam_apap205-6_354 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1994; nam_apap205-6_355 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1995; nam_apap205-6_356 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1996; nam_apap205-6_357 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1996; nam_apap205-6_358 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1996; nam_apap205-6_359 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1996; nam_apap205-6_360 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1997; nam_apap205-6_361 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1997; nam_apap205-6_362 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1998; nam_apap205-6_363 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1998; nam_apap205-6_364 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1998; nam_apap205-6_365 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - The Open Door Community -Hospitality, 1999; nam_apap205-6_366 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Oregon Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1996-1997; Undated; nam_apap205-6_367 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Oregon Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1996-1997; nam_apap205-6_368 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Oregon Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1997; nam_apap205-6_369 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Oregon Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1997; nam_apap205-6_370 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Oregon Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty - newsletter, 1998; nam_apap205-6_371 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Parents of Murdered Children, 1991; 1994; nam_apap205-6_372 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Partison Defense Committee, 1990; Undated; nam_apap205-6_373 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - PAX Christie, 1993; 1995-1997; Undated; nam_apap205-6_374 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - PAX Christie -Catholic Peace Voice, 1995; nam_apap205-6_375 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - PAX Christie -Catholic Peace Voice, 1995; nam_apap205-6_376 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - PAX Christie -Catholic Peace Voice, 1996; nam_apap205-6_377 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Peace CENTER, 1997-1999; nam_apap205-6_378 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Peace on Earth News, 1992-1994; nam_apap205-6_379 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Peacework, 1994; nam_apap205-6_380 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Pennsylvania Abolitionists United Agasint the Death Penalty, 1997-1999; Undated; nam_apap205-6_381 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Pennsylvania Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty, 1995; nam_apap205-6_382 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - People Against Racist Terror -Turning the Tide, 1993; nam_apap205-6_383 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - People of Faith Against the Death Penalty -Take Actions Not Lives, 1998; nam_apap205-6_384 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - The Phoenix, 1998; nam_apap205-6_385 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Pilgrimage Peace and Justice Center -Pilgrimage News, 1990; nam_apap205-6_386 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Presbyterian Criminal Justice Program -Justice Jottings, 1990; nam_apap205-6_387 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Presbyterian Criminal Justice Program -Justice Jottings, 1992; nam_apap205-6_388 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Presbyterian Criminal Justice Program -Justice Jottings, 1996; nam_apap205-6_389 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Presbyterian Criminal Justice Program -Justice Jottings, 1997; nam_apap205-6_390 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Presbyterian Criminal Justice Program -Justice Jottings, 1997; nam_apap205-6_391 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Presbyterian Criminal Justice Program -Justice Jottings, 1998; nam_apap205-6_392 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Presbyterian Criminal Justice Program -Justice Jottings, 1998; nam_apap205-6_393 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Prison Legal News, 1995; nam_apap205-6_394 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Prison Legal News, 1997; nam_apap205-6_395 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Prisoner and Community Together (PACT), 1993; 1996; nam_apap205-6_396 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Prisoner and Community Together -PACT Newsletter, 1993; nam_apap205-6_397 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Prisoner and Community Together -PACT Newsletter, 1993; nam_apap205-6_398 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - The Prisoner 's Advocate Newsletter, 1994; nam_apap205-6_399 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Project Hope, 1990; 1992; 1997; Undated; nam_apap205-6_400 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Project Hope -A Christian Perspective, 1995; nam_apap205-6_401 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Project Hope -A Christian Perspective, 1996; nam_apap205-6_402 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Project Hope -A Christian Perspective, 1997; nam_apap205-6_403 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Project Hope -A Christian Perspective, 1998; nam_apap205-6_404 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Project Hope -A Christian Perspective, 1999; nam_apap205-6_405 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Project Hope -On Wings of Hope, 1996; nam_apap205-6_406 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Project Hope -On Wings of Hope, 1997; nam_apap205-6_407 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Project Hope -On Wings of Hope, 1998; nam_apap205-6_408 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Project Hope -On Wings of Hope, 1999; nam_apap205-6_409 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Quixote Center, 1994; nam_apap205-6_410 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Quixote Center, 1995; nam_apap205-6_411 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Quixote Center, 1996; nam_apap205-6_412 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Quixote Center, 1997; nam_apap205-6_413 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Quixote Center, 1998; nam_apap205-6_414 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Quixote Center, 1999; nam_apap205-6_415 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Quixote Center, Undated; nam_apap205-6_416 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - The Radical Party, 1994; nam_apap205-6_417 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Religion and the Death Penalty, Undated; nam_apap205-6_418 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Resist, 1992; nam_apap205-6_419 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Resist, 1994; nam_apap205-6_420 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Resist, 1995; nam_apap205-6_421 (Box 4, Folder 89)